Guide to the Pach Brothers Portrait Photograph Collection 1867-1947, undated (bulk 1880s-1940s) PR 84
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Individual and Family Portraits
  - Abbott, George Abbott, Lyman Adamic, Louis Adams, Maude Aitken, John William Aldrich, Winthrop Williams Alexander, Douglas Alexander, John White Altman, Benjamin Andrews, Avery Delano Andrews, Roy Chapman Angell, James A. Appleton, Daniel (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
  - Arbuckle, Maclyn Archbold, John Dustin Arliss, George Arnold, Conway Hillyer Arthur, Chester Alan Astor, John Jacob Astor, Vincent, Mrs. and Mr. Huntington Astor, William Vincent (2) Atterbury, Grosvenor Auchincloss, James C. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bache, Jules Semon Badger, Oscar Charles (2) Baer, Arthur Bugs Baer, George Frederick Baer, Julius B. Baker, George Fisher Baker, Ray Stannard Baker, Stephen Baldwin, Leroy Wilbur Balfe, Henry Bangs, John Kendrick Banky, Vilma Bannard, Otto Tremont (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
  - Barclay, McClelland Barlow, Peter Barnard, Frederick Augustus Porter Barnes, Thurlow Weed Barrett, R. L. Barrymore, Ethel Barrymore, Ethel, and her first child Barton, Bruce Baruch, Bernard Mannes (2) Baruch, Simon Battle, George Gordon Batonyi, Aurel Baum, Dwight James Baum, Vicki (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    General note
    See: Lert, Vicki Baum
  - Baxter, William Beals, Ralph A. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
  - Beard, Daniel Carter Beatty, Frank Edmund Beck, James Montgomery Beckwith, James Carroll Belasco, David Bell, Alexander Graham Belmont, August Bender, W. J. Benedict, Elias Cornelius Bennett, A. W. Bennett, Barbara Bennett, Constance Berg, A. A. Berg, W. H. Berlin, Ellen Berlin, Irving (2) Bernays, Edward L. Bernstorff, Johann (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
  - Berry, Fred Berwind, Edwin Julius Besler, William George Bethell, Union Noble Beveridge, Albert Jeremiah Bigelow, John Bingham, Alfred Theodore Black, Hugo L. Blackburn, Luke Pryor (2) Blair, Clinton Ledyard Blair, William Reid Bliss, Cornelius Newton Block, Paul Bloom, Edgar Selden Blumenthal, George (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
  - Boissevain, Louis Bok, Edward William Boomer, Lucius Messenger Booth, Maud Ballington Bordoni, Irene Boston, Charles Anderson Boyer, Charles, Mr. and Mrs. Bradley, Omar Nelson Brady, Cyrus, Townsend (2) Brewer, David Josiah Bridges, Robert ("Droch") Brisbane, Arthur Brokaw, Howard Crosby Brokaw, Issac Vail Bromfield, Louis Bromley, Dorothy Dunbar (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
  - Brooks, Frederick Brooks, John E. Brooks, Walter Broughton, Leonard Gaston Brown, William C. Bruere, Henry Bruning, Heinrich Bryan, Albert Payson [Edward?] Bryan, William Jennings Bryant, Joseph Decatur Bryce, James Buck, Frank (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
  - Buckland, Edward Grant Buhler, Joseph S. Bull, George H. Bullock, H. Bunn, B. Franklin Burfeind, Louis H. Burke, Daniel Burke, John Stephen Burlingame, Edward Livermore Burrell, David James Burroughs, John Burton, Harold H. Butler, Nicholas Murray Buttrick, Wallace (Offsite-box 1, Folder 9)
  - Cable, George Washington Callaway, Samuel Rodger Calvert, Catherine Campbell, Oliver A. Cannon, Joseph G. Carl, William Crane Carnegie, Andrew Carnegie, Dale Carpenter, J. Henry Carstairs, C. S. Carty, John J. Casey, J. Schuyler (3) Cashin, William E. Cassini, Igor (Cholly Knickerbocker) Cerf, Bennett A. (Offsite-box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cesnola, Luigi Palma di Chaffee, Adna Romanza Chanler, Lewis S. Chapin, Chester W. Chaplin, Charles Spencer Chase, Harry Woodburn Chase, William Merritt Chauncey, Daniel Chenery, William Childs, George W. and family (Offsite-box 2, Folder 11)
    See also: Box 9, folder 74
  - Christy, Howard Chandler, Mrs. Churchill, Thomas William Clark, Bobby Clark, Champ Clark, John Bates Clarke, Caspar Purdon (Offsite-box 2, Folder 11)
  - Clement, Martin W. Clemens, Samuel (Offsite-box 2, Folder 12)
    See: Twain, Mark
  - Cleveland, Grover Clews, Henry Clyde, William P. Clyde, William Pancoast Cobb, John Blackwell Coffman, De Witt Coghlan, Joseph Bullock Colby, Bainbridge Coleman, Leighton Coler, Bird Sim Coley, B. L. Collier, Robert Joseph (2) Collyer, Bud Collyer, Robert (Offsite-box 2, Folder 12)
  - Colp, Ralph Comstock, Anthony Connor, Joseph P. (2) Conreid, Heinrich Constant, Samuel Victor Conway, Moncure Daniel Coogan, Jackie Coolidge, Calvin Copeland, Royal Samuel Coppers, George H. Corbin, Austin Cortelyou, George Bruce (Offsite-box 2, Folder 13)
  - Cortez, Ricardo Coudert, Frederic Rene Crain, Thomas C. T. Crandell, J. Bradshaw Crane, William Henry Cravath, Paul Drennan Craven, Frank Crawford, Clifton Creelman, James Croker, Edward F. Croker, Richard Cromwell, Doris Duke (Offsite-box 2, Folder 14)
    See: Duke, Doris
  - Cromwell, James H. R. Cromwell, Jarvis Crosby, John Schuyler Crowley, Patrick Edward Crowinshield, Frank Cullman, Howard Curran, Jean A. Curtiss, Julian Wheeler Cutting, Robert Fulton (Offsite-box 2, Folder 15)
  - Dafoe, Allan Daley, Charles Frederick Damrosch, Frank Heino Damrosch, Walter Johannes Daniel, John F. Darlington, Henry Darlington, Thomas Davenport, Frank F. Davenport, Homer Calvin Davis, Henry Gassaway Davis, John William Davis, Lee Parsons Davis, Richard Harding Davis, Varina Howell (Offsite-box 2, Folder 16)
  - Day, Joseph Paul Day, William Louis De Beck, Billy Deegan, William De Forest, Lee De Forest, Robert Weeks Delano, William Adams De Lanoy, William C. De Markoff, Alexander Dempsey, Jack (2) Dempsey, Jack and daughters Depew, Chauncey Mitchell De Prorok, Byron (Offsite-box 2, Folder 17)
    See: Khun de Prorok, Byron
  - De Remer, Ruby Dewey, George (2) Dewey, Thomas Edmund Diamond, Joseph Dike, Norman Staunton Dillon, John Forrest Ditmars, Raymond Lee Ditrichstein, Leo Dix, Dorothy (Offsite-box 2, Folder 18)
    See: Gilmer, Elizabeth Meriwether
  - Dix, John Alden Dix, Morgan (Offsite-box 2, Folder 18)
  - Dodge, Grenville Mellen Dodge, William Earl Donovan, Edward Doolittle, James Douglas, William O. Dowling, Victor James Dribben, S. F. Ducey, Thomas James Duchin, Eddie Duke, Doris Duncan, William Butler Dunlap, Charles E. Dupuy, Herbert Dyer, George R. (Offsite-box 2, Folder 19)
  - Eagles, Jeanne Eastman, George M. Edison, Minna Miller, and son Edison, Thomas Alva (2) (Offsite-box 3, Folder 20)
  - Edwards, William Hanforth Eggleston, George Cary Eisenhower, Dwight D. Elkins, Stephen Benton Elliott, John Lovejoy Engel, Irving M. English, William H., Jr. Errol, Leon Erskine, John Evans, Luther Evans, Robley Dunglison (Offsite-box 3, Folder 20)
  - Fackenthal, Frank D. Fairbanks, Douglas Falconio, Diomede Falls, Dewitt Clinton Farley, James A. Farley, John Farragut, David Glascoe Faskett, James H. Faunce, William Herbert Perry Ferguson, Elsie (2) Fernandes, Bijou Ferrer, Jose (Offsite-box 3, Folder 21)
  - Field, Cortlandt Depeyster Fielding, Benjamin Finch, Edward Ridley (3) Finley, John Huston Fisher, Ham Fisher, Henry Fisher, Irving Fisk, Willard C. Fiske, Bradley Allen Fiske, Haley Fitch, William Clyde (Offsite-box 3, Folder 22)
  - Fitzgerald, Thomas I. Flagg, Elisha, birthday group Flagg, James Montgomery Flanagan, E. J. Flanigan, Horace C. Fleming, Alexander Fleming, John Flint, Austin Flower, Roswell Pettibone Foley, Thomas Folger, Henry Clay (Offsite-box 3, Folder 23)
  - Folk, Joseph Wingate Fornes, Charles Vincent Forster, Henry (2) Fort, John Franklin Fosdick, Harry Emerson Fowler, Thomas Powell Frankfurter, Felix Frelinghuysen, Joseph Sherman French, Daniel Chester French, Seth Barton Freschi, J. J. Frew, W. E. Friedsam, Michael Frissell, Algernon Sydney Frohman, Daniel Gannon, Robert I. (Offsite-box 3, Folder 24)
  - Gardiner, Asa Bird Garfield, Harry Augustus Garfield, James Abram Garfield, John Hayes Garon, Pauline Garver, John Anson Gary, Elbert Henry Gates, Frederick Taylor Gawtry, Lewis Gay, Charles Richard Gayley, James Gaynor, William J. Gerard, James Watson Gibbs, George Sabin (Offsite-box 3, Folder 25)
  - Gibney, Virgil Pendleton (2) Gibson, Charles Dana Gibson, Hugh Gilbert, Cass Gilder, Richard Watson (2) Gildersleeve, Virginia Crocheron (2) Gillette, William Gilman, Daniel Coit Gilmer, Elizabeth Meriwether Gish, Dorothy Glaenzer, Jules and son Goelet, Robert Goethals, George Washington (Offsite-box 3, Folder 26)
  - Goldberg, Joshua L. Goldberg, Rube Golden, John Golding, Samuel H. Goldstein, Israel Goldwater, Sigismund Schulz Gompers, Samuel Goodrich, Caspar Frederick Gordon, Max Gould, Edwin Gould, George Jay Gould [George J.]Children, Lakewood, NJ Gould, Helen Miller (Offsite-box 3, Folder 27)
    See: Shepard, Helen Gould
  - Gove, Charles Augustus Graham, John Graham, William Joseph Grant, Frederick Dent Grant, Ulysses S. Grant, Ulysses S. and family at Long Branch (2) (Offsite-box 3, Folder 28)
  - Grant, Ulysses S. and the George W. Childs family Graves, Arthur H. Greenway, Lt. Greer, David Hummell Grimm, Peter Guernsey, Egbert Guggenheim, Daniel Guggenheim, Murry Guggenheim, Simon Guggenheim, Wil (Offsite-box 3, Folder 28)
  - Haggard, Henry Rider Hague, James Duncan Halsey, William F. Hamilton, Cosmo Hammerstein, Oscar Hammond, Graeme Monroe Hampden, Walter Harding, Warren Gamaliel Hare, James Montgomery Harkness, William Harlow, Jean Harriman, Edward Henry Harriman, W. Averill Harris, Albert Hall Harris, Charles K. Harrison, Benjamin Hart, Thomas C. Hartford, Huntington (Offsite-box 4, Folder 29)
  - Hartman, Louis H. Hartzell, Joseph Crane Hastings, Harold W. Haswell, Charles Haynes Havemeyer, John Craig Hay, John Hayes, Lucy Webb, and children Hayes, Rutherford Birchard (Offsite-box 4, Folder 30)
  - Haynes, John W. Hayward, William Hayward, William, Mrs. Hearst, Millicent Willson, and son Hearst, Phoebe Apperson Hearst, Phoebe Apperson, and grandson Hearst, William Randolph Hearst, William Randolph, Jr. Hecksher, August Hecksher, John G. (Offsite-box 4, Folder 30)
  - Hedges, Job Elmer Hedley, Frank Hegeman, John Rogers Hempel, Frieda Henderson, Leon Henri, Robert Henschel, Charles R. Hepburn, Alonzo Barton Herbert, H. H. Herbert, Victor Higgins, Frank Wayland Hill, James Jerome Hilles, Charles Dewey Hilles, Newell Dwight Hilton, Conrad N. (Offsite-box 4, Folder 31)
  - Hirsch, Rudolph Hirshfield, Harry Hitchcock, Raymond Hoe, Robert Hoffman, Charles Frederick Hoffman, Malvina Hoffman, William Mitchell Holmes, John Haynes (2) Holmes, Oliver Wendell Holt, Hamilton Hood, John Hoover, Herbert Clark (2) Hornblow, Arthur Horwitz, Max Houseman, Frederick Hoving, Walter Howard, Oliver Otis (Offsite-box 4, Folder 32)
  - Hoyt, Colgate Hoyt, Franklin Chase Hoyt, W. Greeley Hubbard, Thomas Hamlin Hudnut, Richard Hughes, Brian G. Hughes, Antoinette Carter Hughes, Charles Evans (2) Hughes, Leonora Hughes, Rupert Hunter, Thomas Huntington, Mr. (Offsite-box 4, Folder 33)
    See: Astor, Vincent, Mrs. and Mr. Huntington
  - Huntington, Ford Hurst, Fannie Hutchinson, A. A. Hutchinson, Woods Huyler, John S. Hyde, James Hazen Hyser, C. L. (Offsite-box 4, Folder 33)
  - Ingersoll, Ralph Ingersoll, Robert Green Isaacs, Stanley M. Jackson, Robert H. Jackson, William H. Jacobi, Abraham Jacobi, Harold, Jr. Jacobi, Lester Jacobs, Charles M. Jansen, N. J. B. Jefferson, Joseph Jeffrey, Edward Turner Jerome, Jerome Klapka Jerome, William Travers (Offsite-box 4, Folder 34)
  - Jesup, Morris Ketchum Johnson, Eastman Johnson, Hiram Warren Johnson, John Albert Johnson, Lyndon Johnston, Justine Jones, E. Clarence Jourdan, James Joy, Leatrice Joyce, Alice Joyce, Peggy Judge, Arline (Offsite-box 4, Folder 35)
  - Kahn, Otto Herman Kahn, Otto, Mrs. Kahn, Roger W. Kearney, James E. Keat, Fred I. Keech, Frank B. Kelland, Clarence Buddington Kelly, John Kelly, William R. Kendall, Messmore Kennedy, D. Keppler, Rudolph Kernochan, Frederic Kerr, John Brown (Offsite-box 4, Folder 36)
  - Keyes, Edward Lawrence (2) Khun de Prorok, Byron Kimball, James Henry King, Ernest J. Kingsley, Darwin Pearl Kinkaid, Thomas C. Kirby, Gustavus T. Knoedler, Charles Knopf, Alfred A. Knox, Philander Chase Koike, Chozo Kress, Claude Washington Kress, Samuel Henry Kreuger, Ivar Kruttschnitt, Julius Kunz, George Frederick (Offsite-box 4, Folder 37)
  - La Farge, Francis W. La Gatta, John Lambert, Eleanor Lamont, Daniel Scott Lamont, Thomas William Langdon, Woodbury Langhorne, Colonel Lanier, Charles Laurel, Kay Lauterbach, Edward Lavelle, Michael J. Law, Walter William Lawes, Lewis E. (Offsite-box 5, Folder 38)
  - Lawrence, Gertrude Lawrence, Paula Leahy, William D. Lee, Frank Augustus Le Fevre, Jay Leggett, Francis Howard Lehman, Herbert H. Lehman, Robert Leipzig, Nat Leipziger, Henry Marcus Lengyel, Emil Lert, Vicki Baum Levey, Ethel Levinthal, Israel H. Levy, Robert Lewis, Sinclair Lewisohn, Adolph (2) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 39)
  - Liebman, Julius Lightner, M. C. Lillie, Beatrice Lincoln, Abraham (Offsite-box 5, Folder 40)
    See: Box 9, folder 74
  - Lincoln, Arthur Lincoln, Lowell Lippman, Walter Lipton, Thomas Livingston, Goodhue, Jr. Lodge, Henry Cabot Loeb, William Longfellow, Ernest Wadsworth Lonsdale, Frederick Low, Seth Lydig, Philip (Offsite-box 5, Folder 40)
  - McAdoo, William McAdoo, William Gibbs McAuliffe, G.W. McBride, Thomas J. McCain, Arthur W. McCall, John A. McCann, Alfred Watterson McCann, Harry McCarroll, William McCardell, Roy L. McCarter, Thomas Nesbitt McCarthy, James A. McClellan, George Brinton McCooey, John H. (2) McCormick, Robert R. McCoy, Paul McDermott, Terrence S. MacDowell, Noah (Offsite-box 5, Folder 41)
  - McFadden, Bernard McGarrah, Gates W. McGraw, John McGraw, John J. McIntosh, Burr William Mack, Norman Edward McKeogh, Arthur McKinley, William (Offsite-box 5, Folder 42)
  - McManus, George McMein, Neysa Moran McMurtry, George B. Mahl, William Mahoney, Jeremiah T. (Offsite-box 5, Folder 42)
  - Mann, William D'Alton Manning, William Thomas (2) Mansfield, Richard (3) Manville, H. Edward Manville, Thomas, Jr. Marconi, Count Marconi, Guglielmo Markham, Edwin Markle, John Marling, Alfred Erskine Marlowe, Julia Marquand, Rube Marshall, Thomas Riley (Offsite-box 5, Folder 43)
  - Martin, Bradley Mathews, A. E. Matthews, Frank A., Jr. Matthews, James Brander Maxim, Hudson Maxwell, Elsa May, Edna May, George O. Mayo, Henry Thomas Martin, Bradley Meighan, Thomas Mellon, Andrew Merrill, W. P. Merry, Glenn N. Metcalfe, James Stetson Milburn, John George Milford-Haven, Marquess of (Prince Louis of Battenburg) Miller, Charles Addison Miller, Kenneth D. Miller, Roswell (Offsite-box 5, Folder 44)
  - Milliken, Gerrish H. Mills, Darius Ogden Mitchel, John Purroy Mitchell, John Mizner, Addison Mizner, Wilson Moen, A. Rene Moffett, Cleveland Langston Moldenhawer, Julius Valdemar Moody, William Henry Moore, Edward R. (Offsite-box 5, Folder 45)
  - Morgan, Edward M. Morgan, J. Pierpont, Sr. Morgan, J. Pierpont, Jr. Morgan, Junius Spencer Morgenthau, Henry, Sr. Morganthau, Henry, Jr. Morosini, Giovanni P. Morosini, Giulia Morris, Dave Hennen (2) Morris, Newbold Morton, Levi Parsons Morton, Paul Mosconi, Charles Munn, Orson Desaix Murphy, Frank Murray, Oscar G. (Offsite-box 5, Folder 46)
  - Naldi, Nita New, Harry Stewart Newman, William H. Nickerson, E. I. Niles, Nathan Eric Nijinski, Madame Nimitz, Chester W. North, Henry Ringling North, John Ringling (Offsite-box 6, Folder 47)
  - Oblensky, Serge O'Brien, Morgan Joseph Odell, Benjamin Barker Odlum, Hortense McQuarrie Ogden, Robert Curtis Ohlandt, B. C. O'Keefe, Walter Olcott, Jacob Van Vechten Olin, Stephen Henry Oliver, Robert Shaw Oppenheim, Edward Phillips O'Rourke, Fidelis O'Rourke, Tex O'Ryan, John F. (Offsite-box 6, Folder 48)
  - Osborn, Henry Fairchild Osborne, A. Perry Osborne, J. W. Osborne, William Church Outcault, Richard Felton Outerbridge, Eugene Harvey Owen, Catherine Dale (Offsite-box 6, Folder 49)
  - Pach, Alfred, Sr. Pach, Alfred, Jr. Pach, Gotthelf Pach, Walter Pach Brothers (Gotthelf, Gustavus, and Oscar) in their studio (Offsite-box 6, Folder 50)
  - Page, Thomas Nelson Palmer, Frederick Paris, Comte de (2) Parker, Alton Brooks (2) Parkhurst, Charles Henry Parrott, J. R. Parsons, Herbert Parsons, William Barclay Patino, Simon Patterson, Robert P. Paul, Maury Peabody, George Foster Peary, Robert Edwin Pecora, Ferdinand (Offsite-box 6, Folder 51)
  - Pedrick, William (2) Pershing, John Joseph (4) Peters, Ralph Pettit, Williams S. Phelps, Henry M. Philbin, Eugene A. Philip, John Woodward Phillips, David Graham Pickford, Mary Pierson, Lewis Eugene Pinney, Alexander Pitkin, A. J. Plant, Morton F. Plant, Philip M., Mr. and Mrs. (Offsite-box 6, Folder 52)
  - Platt, Charles C. Poletti, Charles Polk, Frank Lyon Polk, William Mecklenburg Pollock, Channing Porter, Horace Post, Augustus Post, Regis Henri Potter, Charles Potter, Henry Codman (2) Prentice, William Satterlee Packer Presbrey, Frank Price, Frank J. Prorok, Byron de (Offsite-box 6, Folder 53)
  - Pryor, Roger Atkinson Pugsley, Cornelius Amory Pulitzer, Ralph Pupin, Michael Idvorsky (Offsite-box 6, Folder 53)
  - Quackenbos (Quackenbush), John Duncan Quick, Douglas Randolph, Francis Fitz Rapee, Erno Raven Anton Adolph Ray, Jackson Harvelle Randolph Raymond, Andrew Van Vranken Rea, C. H. Redfield, William Cox Reed, Stanley F. Reichenbach, Harry Reid, Whitelaw Reilly, Edwin Reinecke, F. C. Reynolds, Quentin, Mr. and Mrs (Offsite-box 6, Folder 54)
  - Rhind, John Massey Rhoades, John Harsen Rice, John L. Richard, Oscar Louis Richman, Harry Ridder, Herman Riis, Jacob August Riley, W. E. Ripley, Edward Payson Ritchie, A. A. Rockefeller, John Davison Rodenbough, Theophilus Francis Roebling, Ferdinand W. Rogers, Admiral Roosa, Daniel Bennett St. John (Offsite-box 6, Folder 55)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor Alexander Roosevelt, Eleanor Alexander with her mother Roosevelt, Eleanor Alexander with her bridesmaids Roosevelt, Eleanor Roosevelt (2) Roosevelt, Eleanor Roosevelt as a bride Roosevelt, Franklin Delano Roosevelt, Kermit Roosevelt, Robert Barnwell Roosevelt, Sarah Delano (Offsite-box 6, Folder 56)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore (5) (Offsite-box 7, Folder 57)
    See also: Box 9, folder 75
  - Roosevelt, Theodore with first grandchild Roosevelt, Theodore, Jr. Roosevelt, Theodore, Jr. and Eleanor Alexander (Offsite-box 7, Folder 57)
  - Root, Elihu Root, Oren Rosenman, Samuel Irving Ross, Harold W. Rossiter, Edward Van Wyck Ruppert, Jacob Jr. (2) Rush, Thomas E. Russell, Lillian Russell, Thomas Ruth, George Herman Rutledge, Wiley (Offsite-box 7, Folder 58)
  - Sabin, Charles Hamilton (2) Sage, Margaret Olivia Slocum Saks, Isador Saloman, William Sands, Benjamin Aymar Sarre, Gordon Sartoris, Nellie Grant (stereograph) Satterlee, Herbert Livingston Saunderson, Percy Sayre, Francis B. Scarborough, John Schaefer, R. J. Schieffelin, William Jay (Offsite-box 7, Folder 59)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry Schiff, William Schley, Winfield Scott Schmittberger, J. Schroeder, Seaton Schindler, Raymond C. Schurman, Jacob Gould Schurz, Carl Seligman, Issac Newton Selwyn, Edgar Serviss, Garrett Putman Seton, Ernest Thompson (Offsite-box 7, Folder 60)
  - Shafter, William Rufus Shaw, Albert Sheehan, William Francis Shepard, Helen Miller Gould Sherman, James Schoolcraft(2) Sickles, Daniel Edgar Simkhovitch, Mary Melinda Kingsbury Sims, P. Hal Skinner, Otis Skitt, Alfred Sleeper, Martha Sloan, Margaret Elmendorf Sloan, Samuel and Margaret Elmendorf (Offsite-box 7, Folder 61)
  - Sloane, Henry T. Sloane, John Sloane, William Milligan Sloane-Field Wedding Smith, Alfred Emanuel Smith, Alfred Holland Smith, Charles Stewart Smith, Harold Smith, Herbert Smith, Robert Alexander C. Snyder, John W. Sockman, Ralph I. Soglow, Otto Sohmer, Harry J. Sohmer, Hugo (Offsite-box 7, Folder 62)
  - Spalding, Albert Goodwill Spellman, Francis Cardinal Sperry, Charles Stillman Sprague, Charles Ezra Stead, W. F. Steel, Johannes Steelman, John R. Steffens, Joseph Lincoln Steingut, Irwin Steinway, Theodore Stern, Louis Stetson, Francis Lynde Stimson, Henry Lewis Stires, Ernest Milmore (Offsite-box 7, Folder 63)
  - Stokes, James Graham Phelps Stokes Family Stotesbury, Edward Townsend Stralem, Casimir Stralem, Donald Straus, Ida Straus, Isidor and Ida Straus, Jack I. Straus, Jesse, Mrs. Straus, Nathan Straus, Oscar Solomon Strauss, Oscar Stroock, Solomon M. Sturges, Ralph A. Sulzberger, Frederick Swann, Edward (Offsite-box 7, Folder 64)
  - Taft, Charles Phelps Taft, Henry Waters Taft, Horace Dutton Taft, Helen Herron Taft, William Howard Takamine, Jokighi Talmadge, Constance Talmadge, Norma Tams, J. Frederic Tashman, Lilyan Taussig, Edward David Terwilliger, H. G. Thom, William B. Thomas, E. R. Thomas, Norman Thomas, Olive Thompson, John R. Thompson, Robert Means (Offsite-box 7, Folder 65)
  - Thorley, Charles Tiffany, Louis Comfort Tilford, Frank Tomkins, Calvin Tompkins, Arthur Sidney Topakyan, Haigazoun Hohannes Torrey, Clare Morse Traphagen, J. C. Trask, Spencer Truesdale, M. D. Truesdale, William Haynes Truman, Harry Trumball, Frank Tully, Jim Tunney, Gene Tunney, James Joseph Twain, Mark (2) (Offsite-box 8, Folder 66)
  - Unidentified couple Unidentified group of three with dogs on porch; military trio at encampment on verso Untermyer, Samuel Usher, Nathaniel Reilly Vail, Theodore Newton (Offsite-box 8, Folder 67)
    See also: Box 9, folder 79
  - Valentine, Lewis Joseph Van & Schenk Van Amringe, John Howard Van Bomel, Leroy Allison Van Brunt, John Vandegrift, A.A. Vanderbilt, Cornelius II Vanderbilt, Cornelius III Vanderbilt, Reginald Claypoole Vanderbilt, William Kissam Vanderbilt, William Kissam, Jr. Vandernoot, Julia Van Stone, N. E. Vetlesen, G. N. Villard, Oswald Garrison Vinson, Fred M. Vreeland, Herbert Harold (Offsite-box 8, Folder 67)
  - Wadsworth, James Wolcott, Jr. Wagner, E. F. Waldo, Rhinelander Walker, Betty Compton Walker, Betty Compton and child Walker, James J. Wallack, Lester, and family Warburg, Paul Moritz Warburton, Barclay H., III (Offsite-box 8, Folder 68)
  - Ward, John Quincy Adams Ward, Wilbur Waring, George Edwin, Jr. Warren, James C. Warren, Lindsay Warren, Stafford Washington, Booker T. Wasserman, S. Waterman, Lewis Edson Watson, James E. Watson, Thomas J., Sr. Watson, Thomas, Jr. Watts, Charles H. Webb, Alexander Stewart Webb, Clifton Webb, Creighton Webb, William Seward, and daughter (Offsite-box 8, Folder 69)
  - Weeks, Clarence G. Weiman, Rita Weir, Julian Alden Welldon, Samuel Welling, Richard Ward Greene Wheeler, Bert Wheeler, Joseph White, Horace White, Lawrence Grant White, William A. Whitman, Charles Seymour Whitney, Caspar Whitney, Cornelius Vanderbilt Whitney, John Hay (Offsite-box 8, Folder 70)
  - Wickersham, George Woodward Wilcox, Ella Wheeler (2) Wilcox, William Walter Wiles, Irving Ramsey Wiley, Louis Wilkie, Wendell Williams, John Sharp Williamson, Frederick Ely Wilson, James Grant Wilson, John Moulder Wilson, Woodrow Windels, Paul H. Windsor, Claire (Offsite-box 8, Folder 71)
  - Wingate, George Wood Winninger, Charles Winslow, Cameron McRae Winthrop, Beekman Wise, Henry Alexander Wise, Stephen Samuel (2) Wood, Leonard Woodford, Stewart Lyndon Woodruff, Timothy Lester Woods, Arthur Woodward, William Wu, Ting-Fang (Offsite-box 8, Folder 72)
  - Youmans, Vincent (Offsite-box 8, Folder 73)
  - Zabriskie, George Zabriskie, George Albert Zelcer, Bonnie Glass Zelcer, F. William Zink, Ebert P. Zukor, Adolph (Offsite-box 8, Folder 73)
- Series II: Oversize and Group Portraits
  Series II. Oversize and Group Portraits contains oversize individual, family group, and group portraits of various people associated through corporate, government and social organizations. Corporate group portraits include the Kress, Singer, Sloan, and Woolworth companies, and the 1908 New York Giants baseball team. Government images are President Hayes and President McKinley with their cabinets, and the members of a Public Services Commission. Social groups are represented by a portrait of a fundraising committee for a World War I-era Allied Ball, and two images of the founders of Delta Upsilon fraternity.
  Arranged in two subseries: Individuals and Family Groups; and Corporate Groups